
======================================================================

************************************************************
*Product Name: Rons Artistic Edges
*Copyright Mar 25, 2009
*By: ron deviney (deviney)
 
************************************************************

in this complete package are:
hi-res photoshop files of Pre-made Film Artistic Edge Templates 8"x10" 2400px x 3000px @ 300ppi
 

--------------------------------------
System Requirements:

PC and Mac compatible
Photoshop
  

--------------------------------------
Ownership Statement:

All of this product's content was created by ron deviney (deviney)
These are all made by my the Rons Film Edge brushes, available here at DAZ as well. 
By creating a rectangle and adding the edges and rotating, scaling,adjusting,moving to get the result you want. You can use the alpa channels to make just the edges or the clipping path method discribed. You can go to photoshops help menu to find more info about clipping masks if it is not clear,but if you are a skilled
at photoshop this may seem trivial.Showcase your work in these pre-made Templates or use them in any way that you like.

alpha channel:   Photoshop alpha channels are masks through which you can apply effects. The alpha channel is an 8-bit channel, which means it has 256 levels of gray from 0 (black) to 255 (white). Like masks the white area is active and the black area is masked and 50% gray allows for 50% exposure.

When you use photoshop’s selection tools, you can apply a filter, adjustment, or modification to effect the selected part of the image. An alpha channel is merely a selection to expose a part of the image for modification.

What is useful about alpha channels is that they can be saved, modified or combined. If you Save a selection (Select > Save Selection), it is sent to an alpha channel so that you can reload the selection when you need it.

Like masks you can paint onto the alpha channel with any of the tools using white black or grey. Filters work in the alpha channels allowing you to modify the mask (not the image). 

  
 
--------------------------------------
Installation Instructions:

Photoshop Layers____un-zip these to your favorite location


  

--------------------------------------
Usage Tips or Limitations:

to use in your postwork renders for commercial and non commercial use.

You may use these as a merchant resource

NOT to resale as is Thats FINAL!

So please,please don't make copies,give them away or share.It affects me directly
It also breaks my heart to anyone might be getting my effort for nothing.
If you are a designer,you should know how it feels,too.
Enjoy the collection, but please respect my copyright! 
 

--------------------------------------
Files Included in the Product:
 
readme

Rons Artistic Edges.psd (30 photoshop layers) and Alpha Channels included in channels palette
 

  


====================================================================== Thank You! 
checkout my other products.

And if you use any of my products in your art,post your creation and let people know what your're using.
Thank You,
Ron Deviney 
